{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "In what children's game are participants chased by someone designated \"It\"?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Tag",
		                "Simon Says",
		                "Charades",
		                "Hopscotch"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "On a radio, stations are changed by using what control?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Tuning",
		                "Volume",
		                "Bass",
		                "Treble"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which material is most dense?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Silver",
		                "Styrofoam",
		                "Butter",
		                "Gold"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which state in the United States is largest by area?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Alaska",
		                "California",
		                "Texas",
		                "Hawaii"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What is Aurora Borealis commonly known as?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Fairy Dust",
		                "Northern Lights",
		                "Book of ages",
		                "a Game of Thrones main character"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "In the U.S., if it's not Daylight Saving Time, it's what?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Borrowed time",
		                "Overtime",
		                "Standard time",
		                "Party time"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which part of the body are you most likely to \"stub\"?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Toe",
		                "Knee",
		                "Elbow",
		                "Brain"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which country is largest by area?",
		            "content" : [
		                "UK",
		                "USA",
		                "Russia",
		                "China"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What does the \"F\" stand for in FBI?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Foreign",
		                "Federal",
		                "Flappy",
		                "Face"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "The US declared war on which country after the bombing of Pearl Harbor?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Japan",
		                "Russia",
		                "Germany",
		                "China"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        }
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "An albino gorilla usually has what color fur?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Brown",
		                "Black",
		                "White",
		                "Golden"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "When you enter a situation without a definite plan of action, you are said to be \"playing it by\" what?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Fingertips",
		                "Ear",
		                "Nose",
		                "Mouth"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What is commonly known as the \"Emerald City\" in the United States?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Palos Verdes, CA",
		                "Seattle, WA",
		                "New York, NY",
		                "Dallas, TX"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What is the national emblem of Canada?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Maple Leaf",
		                "Brown Bear",
		                "Maple Syrup",
		                "Waffle"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What is the name of the largest fresh water lake in the world?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Lake Union",
		                "Lake Superior",
		                "Lake Largest",
		                "Lake Goodwin"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        }
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "Which of the following consumer goods is the Gerber Products Co. best known for?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Potato chips",
		                "Fine wines",
		                "Chewing gum",
		                "Baby Food"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "In which of these household appliances would you find a lint screen?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Dishwasher",
		                "Microwave oven",
		                "Clothes dryer",
		                "Trash compactor"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What are the three primary colors?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Red, green, blue",
		                "Magenta, pink, cyan",
		                "Yellow, salmon, brown",
		                "White, grey, black"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "In aviation, what does UFO stand for?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Unified Flying Object",
		                "Unitary Flinging Obsession",
		                "United Flag Opposition",
		                "Unidentified Flying Object"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "In aviation, what does UFO stand for?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Unified Flying Object",
		                "Unitary Flinging Obsession",
		                "United Flag Opposition",
		                "Unidentified Flying Object"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        }
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "What kind of animal traditionally lives in a sty?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Cow",
		                "Pig",
		                "Fox",
		                "Teenager"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "The EPA urges people to produce less waste by engaging in efforts to reduce, reuse and what?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Recycle",
		                "Rewrap",
		                "Repossess",
		                "Retire"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which month has only 28 days (unless it's a leap year)?",
		            "content" : [
		                "March",
		                "September",
		                "June",
		                "Feburary"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which month has only 28 days (unless it's a leap year)?",
		            "content" : [
		                "March",
		                "September",
		                "June",
		                "Feburary"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        }
		    ]
		}
	]
}